<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Leigh Fletcher</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Leigh Fletcher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Giants</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/ice-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/ice-giants/</guid>
      <description>This theme will use existing ground- and space-based observations of the ice giants to prepare for observations with the James Webb Space Telescope (JWST), where guaranteed time observations of both worlds (programme IDs 1248 and 1249) have been awarded and prepared by Dr. Fletcher.
 Ms. Naomi Rowe-Gurney arrived in Leicester in September 2017 to begin a PhD thesis mining the archive of Spitzer observations of both Uranus and Neptune (disc-averaged due to the small angular size of these planets).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter&#39;s Climate Variability</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/jupiter-climate-variability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/jupiter-climate-variability/</guid>
      <description>Recent publications have explored the moist convective plumes responsible for the revival of Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s South Equatorial Belt in 2009-2011 (http://dx.doi.org/10.1016/j.icarus.2017.01.001), the 3-5 year cycle of expansion activity within Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s North Equatorial Belt (http://dx.doi.org/10.1002/2017GL073383), and a review of cyclic activity across all of Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s main belts (http://dx.doi.org/10.1002/2017GL073806).
 Dr. Arrate Antunano-Martin arrived in Leicester in October 2017 and is working with an infrared dataset spanning more than three jovian years (1983-2018) to identify periodicities and their underlying causes in the jovian atmosphere.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturn&#39;s Seasonal Atmosphere</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/saturn-seasonal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/saturn-seasonal/</guid>
      <description>The Cassini mission came to an end in September 2017, and the ERC team at Leicester were involved in a number of media activities associated with the end of mission. Two publications have been prepared by Dr. Fletcher that deal with Cassini infrared spectroscopy spanning the entire mission, 2004 to 2017: the first (published in Nature Astronomy) investigates the evolution of Saturn&amp;rsquo;s tropical oscillations in the equatorial stratosphere, and the substantial perturbation caused by the Great Northern Storm of 2010-2013 (http://dx.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>