<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Leigh Fletcher</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Leigh Fletcher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Ice Giants</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/ice-giants/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/ice-giants/</guid>
      <description>The final GIANTCLIMES work package extends our understanding of planetary atmospheres out to the distant and under-explored Ice Giants, Uranus and Neptune. This theme will use existing ground- and space-based observations of the ice giants to prepare for observations with the James Webb Space Telescope (JWST), where guaranteed time observations of both worlds (programme IDs 1248 and 1249) have been awarded and prepared by Fletcher. Fletcher is supported by ERC-funded PhD student Naomi Rowe-Gurney; and two PDRAs – Michael Roman (for observations) and Jan Vatant d’Ollone (for numerical simulation).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jupiter&#39;s Climate Variability</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/jupiter-climate-variability/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/jupiter-climate-variability/</guid>
      <description>The first work package of the GIANTCLIMES programme explores the atmospheric variability of Jupiter over long spans of time, combining data from Earth-based observatories with new observations from NASA’s Juno spacecraft. During the course of the ERC programme, the PI (Fletcher) was invited to serve as a Participating Scientist on the Juno mission, developing microwave capabilities for the NEMESIS software to explore the jovian atmosphere beneath the clouds. The Jupiter theme is supported by PDRAs Arrate Antunano (2017-Present) and Henrik Melin (2019-Present), alongside STFC-supported PhD student Padraig Donnelly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Saturn&#39;s Seasonal Atmosphere</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/saturn-seasonal/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/project/saturn-seasonal/</guid>
      <description>The second work package of GIANTCLIMES seeks to complete the analysis of Cassini observations of Saturn’s seasonal atmosphere, and to extend the exploration over longer timespans using ground-based observations. This work is supported by Fletcher and by PDRA James Blake, and notable developments so far include:
 Completion of Cassini: The Cassini mission came to an end in September 2017, and the ERC team at Leicester were involved in a number of media activities associated with the end of mission.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>