<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Communities on Leigh Fletcher</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Communities on Leigh Fletcher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 09:14:18 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Conference Organising</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/conferences/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 09:14:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/conferences/</guid>
      <description> Conference and Workshop Organisation  Lead Organiser, UK Solar System Planetary Atmospheres Meeting, February 14th 2020, Royal Astronomical Society. Lead Organiser, Royal Society Discussion Meeting: Ice Giant Systems 2020, January 20th-22nd 2020. Co-Organiser (with John Rogers), Royal Astronomical Society Juno Workshop, May 10th-11th 2018. Received funding from Europlanet. Co-Organiser (with Amy Simon), COSPAR Ice Giants Session B5.4, July 2018, Pasadena, California.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Leadership Positions</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/community1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 09:14:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/community1/</guid>
      <description> Community Leadership  Elected member of the Europlanet Society Board, 2019-Present. Vice Chair of Commission B5 (Outer Planets) of COSPAR, 2018-Present. Vice President, International Commission on Planetary Atmospheres and their Evolution (ICPAE), a sub-division of IAMAS (2011-2015)  Editorial Boards  Associate Editor, Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets, 2019-Present (responsible for giant planet atmospheres papers). Editorial board, Cambridge University Press Planetary Sciences Series, 2019-Present.  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reviewing</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/reviewing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 11 Jul 2019 09:14:18 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/community/reviewing/</guid>
      <description>I have served as a reviewer for a wide range of peer-reviewed publications, proposals, and other committee activities.
Recognition  Associate Editor of Journal of Geophysical Research: Planets (2019-Present) 2017 Editor’s Citation for Excellence in Refereeing - Geophysical Research Letters. 2014 Certificate of Reviewing Excellence from the Editors of Icarus.  Journal Reviews  Icarus Geophysical Research Letters JGR-Planets Nature Geoscience and Nature Astronomy Science Astronomy and Astrophysics Acta Astronautica Monthly Notices of the Royal Astronomical Society Planetary and Space Sciences Astrophysical Journal Letters  Panel Member  Cambridge University Press Planetary Science Series - Editorial Board.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>