<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Group on Planetary Atmospheres</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Group on Planetary Atmospheres</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Leigh Fletcher</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/leigh-fletcher/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 12 Feb 2019 20:02:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/leigh-fletcher/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests  Planetary atmospheres Spectral Inversion and Radiative Transfer Earth-based observations  Biography Dr. Leigh Fletcher is a Planetary Scientist specialising in the exploration of our Solar System&amp;rsquo;s giant planets via robotic spacecraft missions and ground-based astronomical facilities. He is a Royal Society University Research Fellow (URF) and Associate Professor in Planetary Sciences at the University of Leicester. He is a co-investigator on the Cassini mission to Saturn, the JUICE mission to Jupiter, and a passionate advocate for future exploration of the distance Ice Giants.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oliver King</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/oliver-king/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 22:03:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/oliver-king/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Naomi Rowe Gurney</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/naomi-rowe-gurney/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 22:03:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/naomi-rowe-gurney/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests  Planetary atmospheres Spectral Inversion and Radiative Transfer Ice giants  Biography Naomi is a PhD student at the University of Leicester, specialising in the atmospheres of the ice giants, Uranus and Neptune. She uses data from the Spitzer Space Telescope to characterise the stratospheres of the two planets in preparation for the launch of the James Webb Space Telescope (JWST). She is an active member of the JWST UK outreach community and, as a former teacher, is always looking to take part in science communication events.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Padraig Donnelly</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/padraig-donnelly/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 22:02:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/padraig-donnelly/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests  Planetary atmospheres Spectral Inversion and Radiative Transfer Gas giants Earth-based observations  Biography Padraig Donnelly is a postgraduate researcher at the University of Leicester, specialising in the atmosphere of Jupiter. He uses a ground-based dataset from the Very Large Telescope in Chile to characterise the temporal variability in the Jovian troposphere and stratosphere as part of a wider ground support campaign for NASA’s Juno spacecraft providing the much-needed simultaneous mid-infrared measurements for each approach as well as putting these into the context of the entire Jovian year leading up to and including the Juno epoch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Michael Roman</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/michael-roman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 22:02:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/michael-roman/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr. James Blake</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/james-blake/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 22:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/james-blake/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Arrate Antunano</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/arrate-antunano/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:31:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/arrate-antunano/</guid>
      <description>Research Interests  Planetary atmospheres Spectral Inversion and Radiative Transfer Atmospheric dynamics Gas Giants Earth-based observations  Biography Dr. Arrate Antuñano is a post-doctoral research fellow at the University of Leicester, specialising in the long-term variability of Jupiter’s atmosphere. She uses ground-based infrared data from several previous and present instruments mounted on the NASA’s 3-meter Infrared Telescope Facility on Maunakea, Hawai’i, and on the Very Large Telescope in Chile to characterise the temporal variability of Jupiter’s troposphere and stratosphere, by analysing changes in the clouds, aerosols and temperatures.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dr Henrik Melin</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/henrik-melin/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/group/henrik-melin/</guid>
      <description>Henrik is an STFC-supported postdoc in Leicester&amp;rsquo;s planetary atmospheres team.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>