<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Leigh Fletcher</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Leigh Fletcher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:19:57 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Professional Talks</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/professional-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:19:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/professional-talks/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of my professional talks at national and international conferences, workshops, colloquia and other meetings. Invited talks are highlighted in bold, all others are contributed talks.
 ESTEC, December 2017: Giant Planet Exploration with JWST, Invited talk to the JWST Solar System Proposal Workshop.
 British Planetary Science Convention, University of Glasgow, December 2017: Saturn at Northern Summer Solstice: The Grand Finale of the Cassini Mission.
 IAS, Orsay, November 2017: Earth-Based Support for Jupiter Missions: From Juno to JUICE, Invited Talk at the JUICE/MAJIS team meeting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News &amp; Views Articles</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/news-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/news-views/</guid>
      <description>This page lists my contributions to News &amp;amp; Views, Book Reviews, and Popular Science Articles, both in print and online.
 J.H. Rogers, L.N. Fletcher (2019), Notes and News:&amp;lsquo;New Views of Jupiter&amp;rsquo;: Pro-Am collaborations during and beyond the NASA Juno mission, Journal of the British Astronomical Association 128, 321-323.
 Fletcher, L.N. &amp;amp; Rogers, J.H., (2018), Pro–am collaborations improve views of Jupiter, Astronomy &amp;amp; Geophysics, Volume 59, Issue 4, 1 August 2018, Pages 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Peer-Reviewed Articles</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/peer-reviewed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/peer-reviewed/</guid>
      <description>My peer-reviewed journal articles by the numbers:
 155 articles in peer-reviewed journals &amp;amp; books, 31 as lead author (Science, Nature, GRL, Icarus, A&amp;amp;A, ApJ, AJ, MNRAS, Annual Reviews, etc.)
 5 contributions to book chapters, 1 as lead author.
 1 DPhil/PhD thesis!
  Additional information (and metrics) available via PubLons, Google Scholar, NASA ADS, ORCID and ResearchGate.
 Patrick G.J. Irwin, Daniel Toledo, Ashwin S. Braude, Roland Bacon, Peter M.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Publications</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/technical-publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/technical-publications/</guid>
      <description>This page lists my contributions to White Papers, Technical Reports, and Mission Proposals that are not published in peer-reviewed journals.
 James M. Bauer, Stefanie Milam, Gordon Bjoraker, Sean Carey, Doris Daou, Leigh Fletcher, Walt Harris, Paul Hartogh, Christine Hartzell, Amanda Hendrix, Carrie Nugent, Andy Rivkin, Timothy Swindle, Cristina Thomas, Matthew S. Tiscareno, Geronimo Villanueva, Scott Wolk (2019), Planetary Science with Astrophysical Assets: Defining the Core Capabilities of Platforms, submitted to the US Astrophysics Decadal Survey</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>