<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Publications on Leigh Fletcher</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Publications on Leigh Fletcher</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:19:57 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Talks</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/professional-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:19:57 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/professional-talks/</guid>
      <description>This is a list of my professional talks at national and international conferences, workshops, colloquia and other meetings. Invited talks are highlighted in bold, all others are contributed talks.
 ESA&amp;rsquo;s Voyage 2050 Workshop, Madrid, October 29th 2019: Invited presentation of our white paper on *Ice Giant Systems: Scientific Potential of Missions to Uranus and Neptune.*
Big Beasts -first up is @LeighFletcher @uniofleicester with a mission to explore the Ice Giants Uranus and Neptune #voyage2050 -“exoplanets in our backyard” pic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Journal Articles</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/peer-reviewed/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/peer-reviewed/</guid>
      <description>My peer-reviewed journal articles by the numbers:
 166 articles in peer-reviewed journals &amp;amp; books, 32 as lead author (Science, Nature, GRL, Icarus, A&amp;amp;A, ApJ, AJ, MNRAS, Annual Reviews, Space Science Reviews, etc.)
 5 contributions to book chapters, 1 as lead author.
 1 DPhil/PhD thesis!
  Additional information (and metrics) available via PubLons, Google Scholar, NASA ADS, ORCID and ResearchGate.
 A.A. Simon, L.N. Fletcher, C. Arridge, D.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>News &amp; Views Articles</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/news-views/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/news-views/</guid>
      <description>This page lists my contributions to News &amp;amp; Views, Book Reviews, and Popular Science Articles, both in print and online.
 J.H. Rogers, L.N. Fletcher (2019), Notes and News:&amp;lsquo;New Views of Jupiter&amp;rsquo;: Pro-Am collaborations during and beyond the NASA Juno mission, Journal of the British Astronomical Association 128, 321-323.
 Fletcher, L.N. &amp;amp; Rogers, J.H., (2018), Pro–am collaborations improve views of Jupiter, Astronomy &amp;amp; Geophysics, Volume 59, Issue 4, 1 August 2018, Pages 4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Papers</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/technical-publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 11 Feb 2019 21:04:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/publication/technical-publications/</guid>
      <description>This page lists my contributions to White Papers, Technical Reports, and Mission Proposals that are not published in peer-reviewed journals.
 Olivier Mousis, David H. Atkinson, Richard Ambrosi, Sushil Atreya, Don Banfield, Stas Barabash, Michel Blanc, Thibault Cavalié, Athena Coustenis, Magali Deleuil, Georges Durry, Francesca Ferri, Leigh Fletcher, Thierry Fouchet, Tristan Guillot, Paul Hartogh, Ricardo Hueso, Mark Hofstadter, Jean-Pierre Lebreton, Kathleen E. Mandt, Heike Rauer, Pascal Rannou, Jean-Baptiste Renard, Agustin Sanchez-Lávega, Kunio Sayanagi, Amy Simon, Thomas Spilker, Ethiraj Venkatapathy, J.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>