<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engagements on Planetary Atmospheres</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engagements on Planetary Atmospheres</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:14:54 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Press Coverage</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/press-coverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:14:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/press-coverage/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Talks</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/public-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:09:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/public-talks/</guid>
      <description>General Audience  New Scientist Live, Excel Centre London, October 11th 2019: Invited presentation to ~800 attendees at NSL2019, Lifting Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s Cloudy Veil: Our Exploration of the Giant Planet. Pint of Science, Leicester, May 20th 2019: Onwards to the Ice Giants presentation at Manhattan 34.  Astronomy Societies  Nene Valley Astronomical Society (Northamptonshire), September 17th 2018, Exploring the Weather of the Giant Planets. British Astronomical Association Weekend, July 7th 2018, University of Warwick, Exploring the Weather of the Giant Planets via Professional-Amateur Collaboration Heart of England Astronomical Society, April 26th 2018, New Views of the Jupiter System.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exhibitions and Museums</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/exhibitions-and-museums/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:08:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/exhibitions-and-museums/</guid>
      <description>Planets 2018: Reimagining Holst&amp;rsquo;s Planets Suite a Century On: I was invited to work on a Live Music Sculpture event produced by Sound UK and funded by Arts Council England, National Lottery and RVW Trust. I was tasked with working with composer Richard Bullen to create a new composition of Holst&amp;rsquo;s Jupiter, inspired by our scientific discoveries over the past century. These were performed to a live audience in four planetariums (Greenwich, Winchester, Bristol and Birmingham) by the Ligeti Quartet, and I provided an introduction to planetary science at the Thinktank Museum, Birmingham, on October 2nd 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV and Radio</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/tv-and-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:08:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/tv-and-radio/</guid>
      <description> Television Sky at Night  May 2018: Interviewed at the Royal Astronomical Society, providing an update on the latest discoveries from NASA&amp;rsquo;s Juno mission.  Podcasts  ITN Podcast on Exoplanets (commissioned by audible.com) - recorded in Leicester on October 10th 2019.
 Space Boffins: recorded a discussion of future missions to the Ice Giants at the UK Space Conference, September 25th 2019.
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:07:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/schools/</guid>
      <description>Space School: The University of Leicester&amp;rsquo;s Space School celebrated its 30th anniversary in 2019, and I was invited to give a lecture on my planetary research to their &amp;ldquo;senior school&amp;rdquo; (16-18 year olds) in August 2019, focussing on future missions to the Ice Giants. I previously provided a lecture at the Space School 2016, on exploring giant planet atmospheres.
Space School UK are loving hearing about the exciting planetary science research of @LeighFletcher!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Writing</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/science-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:07:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/science-writing/</guid>
      <description>Science Blogs I regularly provide scientific content for online websites, including the following:
 Planetary Wanderings - personal blog maintained since 2007. Leicester to Jupiter - creator of a blog at the University of Leicester to celebrate UK involvement in the Juno mission. The Conversation - including several articles on the Juno mission to Jupiter and the future exploration of Europa. Planetary Society - including Saturn&amp;rsquo;s hexagon, Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s meteorology, and Europa&amp;rsquo;s plumes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>