<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Engagements on Planetary Atmospheres</title>
    <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Engagements on Planetary Atmospheres</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:14:54 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Press Coverage</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/press-coverage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:14:54 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/press-coverage/</guid>
      <description>Press Releases  Press Release on Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s Equatorial Disturbances (Dec 19th 2018): Press-released work from my postdoc, Arrate Antunano, by the University of Leicester: https://le.ac.uk/news/2018/december/19-planetary-astronomers-identify-cycle-spectacular-disturbances-jupiters-equator ESA Press Release (September 4th, 2018): Press release on our Nature Communications article, discovering that Saturn&amp;rsquo;s famous hexagon may tower above the clouds. Press release available here. NASA Press Release (June 25th 2018): Press release on my team&amp;rsquo;s plans to use the James Webb Space Telescope to reveal new insights into Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s Great Red Spot, available here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Public Talks</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/public-talks/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:09:04 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/public-talks/</guid>
      <description>General Audience  New Scientist Live, Excel Centre London, October 11th 2019: Invited presentation to ~800 attendees at NSL2019, Lifting Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s Cloudy Veil: Our Exploration of the Giant Planet. Pint of Science, Leicester, May 20th 2019: Onwards to the Ice Giants presentation at Manhattan 34. Cassini End of Mission activities (September 2017): presentation and Q&amp;amp;A at National Space Centre; BBC Breakfast Appearance; Sky at Night show on end of Cassini; BBC East Midlands live from Space Centre.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exhibitions and Museums</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/exhibitions-and-museums/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:08:34 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/exhibitions-and-museums/</guid>
      <description>Planets 2018: Reimagining Holst&amp;rsquo;s Planets Suite a Century On: I was invited to work on a Live Music Sculpture event produced by Sound UK and funded by Arts Council England, National Lottery and RVW Trust. I was tasked with working with composer Richard Bullen to create a new composition of Holst&amp;rsquo;s Jupiter, inspired by our scientific discoveries over the past century. These were performed to a live audience in four planetariums (Greenwich, Winchester, Bristol and Birmingham) by the Ligeti Quartet, and I provided an introduction to planetary science at the Thinktank Museum, Birmingham, on October 2nd 2018.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TV and Radio</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/tv-and-radio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:08:17 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/tv-and-radio/</guid>
      <description>Television General  BBC The Planets (October 24th 2018): Three hours of filming in Knoxville Tennessee on all four giant planets, preparing a BBC/Nova documentary series all about the Solar System, called The Planets. Appeared briefly at the end of episode 5 (Into the Darkness), but more prominently in the international version. Provided consultation for BBC researchers from July-October 2018 for the full show.
 Child Genius - Channel 4 (June 2018): Provided consultation to Wall-to-Wall media in their preparation for a Cassini-Huygens round in the final episode of Child Genius.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schools</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/schools/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:07:41 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/schools/</guid>
      <description>Space School: The University of Leicester&amp;rsquo;s Space School celebrated its 30th anniversary in 2019, and I was invited to give a lecture on my planetary research to their &amp;ldquo;senior school&amp;rdquo; (16-18 year olds) in August 2019, focussing on future missions to the Ice Giants. I previously provided a lecture at the Space School 2016, on exploring giant planet atmospheres.
Space School UK are loving hearing about the exciting planetary science research of @LeighFletcher!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Science Writing</title>
      <link>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/science-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 May 2019 21:07:01 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://leighfletcher.github.io/engagement/science-writing/</guid>
      <description>Science Blogs I regularly provide scientific content for online websites, including the following:
 Planetary Wanderings - personal blog maintained since 2007. Leicester to Jupiter - creator of a blog at the University of Leicester to celebrate UK involvement in the Juno mission. The Conversation - including several articles on the Juno mission to Jupiter and the future exploration of Europa. Planetary Society - including Saturn&amp;rsquo;s hexagon, Jupiter&amp;rsquo;s meteorology, and Europa&amp;rsquo;s plumes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>